<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[分类：dropbox | Liang's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://lcsoft2009.github.io/blog/categories/dropbox/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://lcsoft2009.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-12-19T15:23:38+09:00</updated>
  <id>http://lcsoft2009.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[kiyoto]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[第三篇文章]]></title>
    <link href="http://lcsoft2009.github.io/blog/di-san-pian-wen-zhang.html"/>
    <updated>2014-12-18T12:14:22+09:00</updated>
    <id>http://lcsoft2009.github.io/blog/di-san-pian-wen-zhang</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<ul id="markdown-toc">
  <li><a href="#a-little-intro">1. a little intro</a>    <ul>
      <li><a href="#infrequent-blogger">1.1 infrequent blogger</a></li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li><a href="#this-time-due-to-the-platform">2. This time due to the platform</a></li>
  <li><a href="#octopress-and-my-current-workflow">3. Octopress and my current workflow</a></li>
  <li><a href="#content">3content</a></li>
  <li><a href="#hello">4 hello</a></li>
  <li><a href="#dropbox">3.Dropbox</a></li>
</ul>

<h1 id="a-little-intro">1. a little intro</h1>

<p>&#8220;` cpp C++ for loop http://www.baidu.com 转到百度 
#include <iostream>
using namespace std;</iostream></p>

<p>int main ()
{
   // for loop execution
   for( int a = 10; a &lt; 20; a = a + 1 )
   {
       cout « “value of a: “ « a « endl;
   }</p>

<p>return 0;
}
&#8220;`
<!-- more --></p>

<h2 id="infrequent-blogger">1.1 infrequent blogger</h2>
<p>I’m an infrequent blogger, I find I can’t write routinely and my previous attempts at starting blogs all failed miserablyƒ. However there are many personal sites out there that I admire with some great content which always encourages me to try again - so here goes, another attempt starting in 2013. 
大连夜景
 <img src="/images/dalian/1.jpg">
  <img src="/images/dalian/2.jpg">
   <img src="/images/dalian/3.jpg">
    <img src="/images/dalian/4.jpg"></p>

<h1 id="this-time-due-to-the-platform">2. This time due to the platform</h1>
<p>workflow and Apps I’m using I feel I may be a little bit more creative.</p>

<div class="foo">
  <table>
    <thead>
      <tr>
        <th>Default aligned</th>
        <th style="text-align: left">Left aligned</th>
        <th style="text-align: center">Center aligned</th>
        <th style="text-align: right">Right aligned</th>
      </tr>
    </thead>
    <tbody>
      <tr>
        <td>First body part</td>
        <td style="text-align: left">Second cell</td>
        <td style="text-align: center">Third cell</td>
        <td style="text-align: right">fourth cell</td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
        <td>Second line</td>
        <td style="text-align: left">foo</td>
        <td style="text-align: center"><strong>strong</strong></td>
        <td style="text-align: right">baz</td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
        <td>Third line</td>
        <td style="text-align: left">quux</td>
        <td style="text-align: center">baz</td>
        <td style="text-align: right">bar</td>
      </tr>
    </tbody>
  </table>

</div>

<p><i class="fa fa-camera-retro fa-5x"></i> fa-camera-retro</p>

<p><code>ruby Discover if a number is prime http://www.noulakaz.net/weblog/2007/03/18/a-regular-expression-to-check-for-prime-numbers/ Source Article
class Fixnum
  def prime?
    ('1' * self) !~ /^1?$|^(11+?)\1+$/
  end
end
</code></p>

<p><img src="http://placekitten.com/890/280">
<img class="left" src="http://placekitten.com/320/250" title="Place Kitten #2" >
<img class="right" src="http://placekitten.com/300/500" width="150" height="450" title="Place Kitten #3" >
<img class="right" src="http://placekitten.com/300/500" width="150" height="550" title="‘Place Kitten #4’ ‘An image of a very cute kitten’" ></p>

<h1 id="octopress-and-my-current-workflow">3. Octopress and my current workflow</h1>
<center><img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/22370970/blogimages/octopress.jpg"></center>
<p>I like to get my hands dirty, even in my current day job (which is strictly management) I can’t get by without some hands on, whether that be coding, diagnosing or generally rolling my sleeves up and getting stuck in, so <a href="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</a> with its strap line of ‘A blogging framework for hackers’ got my attention last year and after inspecting closely and reading other people’s experiences with it, I decided to give it a go.</p>

<p>As of this post I’m using Octopress on Mac OSX Mountain Lion, running on a MacBook Pro. The MBP has Wake On Demand enabled so I can tunnel in from anywhere I have an internet connection with my chosen SSH iOS App and generate and deploy to Github Pages (where this blog is currently hosted).</p>

<h1 id="content">3content</h1>
<p>I love <a href="http://daringfireball.net/projects/markdown/">Markdown</a>, creating content with it is a joy and I don’t have to code while I write or use awful CMS, it feels natural and the syntax is easy to remember. I also can’t recommend highly enough <a href="www.iawriter.com/">iA Writer</a>. It’s clean, minimal interface and focus on text along with its support for Markdown and integration with Dropbox is a must have on iOS for anyone with a similar setup. </p>

<h1 id="hello">4 hello</h1>
<p>dasjhdjsjsdhkjsdsfsdfkjsdcksjd
scs
dc
sd
sd
c
sad</p>

<h1 id="dropbox">3.Dropbox</h1>
<p>The entirety of this site is stored within my Dropbox account, this means that I can access and create posts using iA Writer and have them synced instantly back to my Mac. With Dropbox keeping <a href="https://www.dropbox.com/help/11/">30 day snapshots</a> too, I have assurances that if I mess something up, I can revert back to a previous version of a configuration, stylesheet, markdown post or piece of code with ease.</p>

<p>I’m also hosting most of the sites images from Dropbox too, I love the idea that I have complete control and ownership of everything.
### theming
The default Octopress theme for me is too ugly and is found on so many other Octopress blogs that I just had to move away from it. I couldn’t find a theme I liked ‘out of the box’ so therefore went with <a href="http://zespia.tw/Octopress-Theme-Slash/">the Slash theme</a> and started customising from there to get a clean, minimalistic feel. I’ve been hugely influenced by the design of <a href="http://blog.gesteves.com/">Guillermo Esteves blog</a> (also using Octopress), I think it’s damn near perfect, so I’m aiming to get a similar look and feel over time.
### what next?</p>
<center><img src="https://www.evernote.com/shard/s278/sh/0710427a-e7f5-495c-86aa-a07b70c97fb8/8142fdb2824c08833e348c83bdc03664/res/f2ef00f3-773b-4f1b-ab92-5130fbba4339/skitch.png"></center>

<p>I’ve purchased a <a href="http://www.raspberrypi.org/">Raspberry Pi</a> this weekend, the latest 512Mb edition to be exact, so my plan going forward is to use the Pi as my Octopress staging platform. It’s going to be ideal as a low powered always on server I can SSH in to, no longer having to rely on my MacBook Pro and as of this post I have 1 week to wait before I get my hands on it and start hacking away - I can’t wait and will no doubt share the experiences going forward.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starting With Octopress]]></title>
    <link href="http://lcsoft2009.github.io/blog/di-%5B%3F%5D-pian-wen-zhang.html"/>
    <updated>2013-01-20T16:33:00+09:00</updated>
    <id>http://lcsoft2009.github.io/blog/di-[?]-pian-wen-zhang</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="a-little-intro">a little intro</h3>
<p>I’m an infrequent blogger, I find I can’t write routinely and my previous attempts at starting blogs all failed miserably. However there are many personal sites out </p>

<script type="math/tex; mode=display">
f'\left( x\right) = \lim _{x\rightarrow 0}\dfrac {f\left( x+\Delta x\right) - f\left( x\right)}{\Delta x}
</script>

<!-- more -->
<p>there that I admire with some great content which always encourages me to try again  so here goes, another attempt starting in 2013. This time due to the platform, workflow and Apps I’m using I feel I may be a little bit more creative.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
